

FRONT END DEVELOPER

### **Details**

Bucharest, 061075 Romania 0757111844 moscaliuc.madalin@yahoo.com

NATIONALITY

Romanian

DRIVING LICENSE

В

DATE OF BIRTH

22 Nov 1994

#### Links

**Instagram** 

<u>Facebook</u>

Personal Portfolio

# **Skills**

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

ReactJS

**Communication Skills** 

Ability to Multitask

Computer Skills

**Critical Thinking** 

Adaptability

### Languages

Romanian

English

### **Profile**

Meticulous Entry - Level Front End Developer with 1 year of front end experience and passion for responsive website design. With a passion for both personal growth and for software development, I attended a 1000+ hour coding course to learn new languages while sharpening existing skills. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented engineering team to develop quality solutions.

# **Employment History**

# Junior Front End Developer, Freelancer, Bucharest

2021 - PRESENT

- Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills on a larger development team.
- Good Skills with HTML CSS JavaScript Bootstrap (self-taught).
- Utilized HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create responsive landing pages and web applications.
- Learned front-end object-oriented programming to develop client server systems.
- Design and develop features to meet customer requirements.

# Millitary Officer - Intelligence Officer, Ministry of National Defence - Romania. Bucharest

JULY 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

- Wrote reports based on collected intelligence data from various open sources to include local and other partners.
- Collected information from various communications and analyzed it for meaningful information.
- Analyzed and evaluated intelligence to assess developments, trend and threat implications associated with national security environment.
- Served as Intelligence Officer to Ministry of National Defence on the employment of intelligence collection assets resulting in surveillance and intelligence gathering from all available sources.

# Police Officer - Intelligence Officer, Ministry of Justice - Romania, Bucharest

AUGUST 2017 - JULY 2020

- My role as an Intelligence Officer with the Ministry of Justice was to serve as an all-crimes / all-threats intelligence raports for the Ministry of Justice and participating agencies.
- My duties included information sharing, collecting, analyzing and disseminating Intelligence to those requesting intelligence raports in a timely manner in order to protect the state and critical infrastructures of Ministry of Justice.
- Applied advanced tools and techniques to inteligence cycle, addressing complex challenges with emphassis on data analytics and data visualization.

# Education

Master of Science in National Security and Intelligence Management, "Mihai Viteazul" National Intelligence Academy, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Identifying and applying management position for achieving the organization's goals.
- Planning action within operation and mission meant to contribute to national security.

French

#### **Hobbies**

Cycling, watching movies, learning, computer programming

analyzing and projecting landmarks in national security policies.

 Applying group relation tehnique; developing empathic abilities in interpersonal

communication and taking specific roles in team work.

# Bachelor of Security Science and National Security Intelligence, "Mihai Viteazul" National Intelligence Academy, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2014 - JULY 2017

 Correctly describing and applying the theories, paradigms and methodologies used in

the process of analysing intelligence in the field of national security.

- Identifying (in)security problems and advancing proposals to solve them.
- Establishing benchmarks within some action point plans in order to optimize

intelligence activity in the field of national security.

 Drawing out and applying specific procedures for leadership optimization in military

organisations.

 Establishing planning documents needed in the process of leading the intelligence

activities for national security.

# **Conferences and Seminars**

Scientific Conference - "Alexandru Ioan Cuza" Police Academy, Bucharest

• Rank 3 in the - "Scientific Conference - The Importance of Education in the knowledge-based society" organisez by the Romanian Police Academy.

# Scientific Conference - "Mihai Viteazul" National Intelligence Academy, Bucharest

Participation - Scientific communication session - "Security and globalization.
Romania relevant player in regional security ".

# International Scientific Conference - Military Tehnical Academy, Bucharest

• Participation to the International Scientific Conference "Circle 2015 Students"